Contact

+54 9 3516077008 (Mobile) piazzajignacio@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/joseipiazza (LinkedIn) joseignaciopiazzacv.vercel.app/ (Company)

Top Skills

phyton

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Python

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Spanish (Native or Bilingual)
Italian (Professional Working)
French (Elementary)

Certifications

Elastic Cloud Infrastructure: Scaling and Automation

Essential Cloud Infrastructure: Foundation

Create and Manage Cloud Resources

Ansible: Playbooks Deep Dive Certified Kubernetes Administrator (CKA)

Jose Piazza

SysOps | DevOps Engineer en ASAPP Argentina

Summary

Experience in software engineering principles, at automation and orchestration, specifically around server deployment and Configuration/customization.

10 years of experience in IT, The last 6 years I developed my carrier of DevOps, I am comfortable working autonomously where required, though endeavour to contribute as much as possible in a team environment and actively dedicate time for technical mentoring and collaboration activities amongst my peers. Beyond my immediate team, I liaise closely with project management staff and also provide technical representation to the end customer .I strive when given an opportunity to learn new technologies.

I think that my main strengths are:
Great flexibility and adaptability
Always Willing to learn and improving.
I love the exchange of cultures and experiences.
being all time available for my workmates, if it requires.

Language:
Spanish native
English Advance.
Italian Intermediate
French Beginne

more information --> https://joseignaciopiazzacv.vercel.app/

Experience

ASAPP
Sysops/DevOps Engineer
April 2021 - Present (1 year 2 months)
Uruguay

AWS (vpc, ec2, RDS, redis, autoscaling group, route 53, Elastic Load Balancing, CloudWatch)

GCP (APP engine, compute engine, Kubernetes Engine,Instance Groups, Google cloud storage,Nearline, Coldline, Cloud Sql, cloud Bigquery,Cloud Load Balancing)

Deploying infraestructure in amazon using terraform

K8s /Docker

Python

Helm chart

Terraform: Deploy RDS database in AWS in order to be connected to sonarqube server (deployed by helmfile)

Integration of Sonarqube with Okta and github and circle-ci , as well as with codefresh

Ansible playbooks for server/resources provisioning in VMWARE Monitoring with Graphana ,Prometheus and Datadog

Pagerduty

Gitlab-ci

Implementation of Backstage.io

Gitbub, Circle-ci, Spinnaker, codefresh

Atos

6 years 11 months

Automation Engineer
January 2020 - Present (2 years 5 months)

Córdoba, Argentina

- -Customize and implement the laaS Orchestration Tool like Ansible to automate apps and infrastructure quickly.
- -Redhat 7 and 8
- Python scripting
- JavaScript and to perform integration vSphere REST Api-
- Short Docker experience.
- Administration of VMware.
- GCP
- Kubernetes

Infrastructure Management Senior Analyst at Atos July 2015 - December 2019 (4 years 6 months) Argentina

Aix/Red hat Admin

Management of virtual environment shaped by VMware and redhat Linux servers for US company.

Knowledge in Javascript, CSS, HTML, and nodeJs

AWS(EBS, EC2,S3)

Customize and implement the laaS Orchestration Tool like Ansible to automate apps and infrastructure quickly.

python scripting

Xerox

Infrastructure Management Senior Analyst at XEROX October 2011 - June 2015 (3 years 9 months)

Administration of unix systems AIX for DCPM, Calpine, Hallmark and MWV.

Big environment

Incident and change management.

VMWARE vSphere 5 fundamental

Linux RHEL v5/6 installation, upgrade and administration

Linux RHEL v5 performance tuning

Logical Volume Manager (LVM) management, administration and configuration

Hardware Management Console (HMC) administration and configuration.

Network Installation Manager (NIM) configuration.

Virtual I/O servers and Lpar management, installation and configuration.

leading project about installation of nimbus

Working in transition period of new customer, building and configuration servers from scratch.

Focal Point of clients like meadwestvaco, DCPM and Calpine.

OS Update in AIX servers .

Upgrading Hardware Management Console (HMC) version.

High Availability Clusters PowerHA/HACMP: Installation, Configuration,

Management, Troubleshooting, Cluster Tests Exercises, Monitoring and Health Checking.

Multipath SAN driver management: sdd, sddpcm, HDLM, Powerpath, ESS, MPIO.

Big SAN migration to VMAX, ownership, planning, scheduling.

Migration Project from AIX v5L/6 to Linux RHEL v5 – Major project where over 140 AIX v6 servers have been migrated to Linux v5.

Storage migration Project – From Hitachi to SVC.

Storage migration project – From Clarion to VMAX.

AIX DR Project using SRDF EMC SAN replication – Yearly project with 23 LPARs, dual VIOS, HACMP nodes, dual HMC. A complete configuration from

scratch needs to be make since there is no dedicated hardware in the DR site

for this project, the configuration includes: build all LPARS and VIOS profiles, NPIV and VSCSI devices, a complete network reconfiguration, modify HACMP scripts in order to configure HA failover among other AIX OS setups.

Steady state, on-call support and Client Leader Role. Incident and problem management.

Infrastructure Architect Projects - New clients/Datacenter migration planning and execution.

Chef, Docker Admisnitration.

IBM

Unix System Administrator At IBM Cordoba Argentina. November 2008 - November 2011 (3 years 1 month)

Administration of unix systems (Solaris, Linux, HP-UX and AIX) for Novartis customer worldwide.Big environment of 1200+ servers.

Incident and change management.

Logical Volume Manager (LVM) management, administration and configuration Hardware Management Console (HMC) administration and configuration.

Network Installation Manager (NIM) configuration.

Virtual I/O servers and Lpar management, installation and configuration.

HP-SIM installation and configuration.

SAMBA installation and basic configuration.

LVM configuration and troubleshooting. Striped LV, Mirrored LV and snapshot Volumes.

GFS – Global File System configuration and administration

Linux migration project from v4 to v5 – Major project with 300 Linux servers involved.

HP

Networking Security Services.

May 2007 - November 2008 (1 year 7 months)

In charge of administrate ISA servers 2004 version for the LAN Company.

Access management of users accounts , on platform Windows 2003 and Linux/Unix.

Administration of files shares.

Systems managed: Linux/AIX/HP-UX

- Create/Modify IDs.
- Create/Modify and control access to groups on Systems (Linux /Unix/ Windows)
- Folder permissions
- ACL

- Problem solving related to Security in both Linux and Windows

WorldNet

Technical Support March 2006 - January 2007 (11 months)

Installation and configuration of operative systems, like windows 95,98,2000,2003 and XP. As well as also Linux, more specifically Red hat. Planification implementation and administration of networking, both kind of networking, wired and wireless.

Education

Universidad Nacional de Córdoba Bachelor's Degree, Linux, Based on Ubuntu · (2014 - 2014)

In-company LPAR and VIO level I training course (IBM) LPAR/VIO · (2010 - 2010)

In-company Business english training course (IBM) english, English · (2008 - 2009)

Capacitación IT Solaris 10 Administrator, Systems · (2007 - 2008)

Online Academic of Villa Maria City English, English (2004 - 2006)